Will you come home for dinner tonight?
The suit will arrive this afternoon.
I want you to try it on.
I have a social engagement tonight.
It's up to you.
As long as you like it,
I will like it.
OK.
I'm leaving.
I've found it.
I went to check it out
after you called me the other day.
The Sunshine Orphanage closed 26 years ago.
The director emigrated overseas.
I found an employee from that time.
He said the orphanage didn't have any management issues.
It was all a sudden decision made by Director Li.
This is Director Li's
address in Singapore.
Coincidentally,
her daughter is the manager of Golden Thread's branch.
But Ms. Li rarely contacts her.
As for this matter,
don't worry,
I'm a tight-lipped person.
But why do you suddenly investigate this?
I'm investigating for a friend.
He was adopted by this orphanage.
With the wedding coming up,
you're investigating your friend's background.
Do you need my help?
No.
I gave him the information,
he'll handle it himself.
By the way,
there's nothing unusual
about your brother-in-law.
Then we need to investigate thoroughly,
and make sure nothing is overlooked.
Do you hope I find something
or find nothing?
Of course, it's best to find nothing.
Hello?
I'll be there soon.
What's wrong?
Mumu got into a fight at school.
I have to go there.
Is your kindergarten a zoo?
This brat must be expelled today.
Please calm down.
Lu Mu's parents will be here soon.
Mumu,
who started it?
He deserved it.
He stole the toy car my uncle bought me.
Did you hear that?
This wild child
must be expelled immediately.
Principal,
check the surveillance.
You better hope my son started it first.
Otherwise,
I'll break your arms and legs.
Look at her.
Is she even making sense?
Look at what Lu Mu did to my child!
Let go!
What do you want?
Yan, take the child and go.
If this isn't resolved today,
don't even think about leaving!
Don't make me repeat myself!
What else do you want?
Huh?
What do you want?
Calm down.
Take the child to the hospital first.
We'll handle
the rest.
What?
You want to get rid of us like this?
We're not short of money.
Why did she leave?
I'm telling you,
I'm not afraid of your grandma.
Don't think you can do anything
just because you're rich.
There are
many rich families in this world.
Tell Lu Qianqian
to bring Lu Mu here
and apologize to my son within three days.
Okay.
Let's go.
Who did this?
I'm calling the police.
I did it.
Crazy woman.
What do you want?
My husband is...
Mom, are you okay?
You'll kill her if you keep beating her.
I, Lu Qianqian, have never
said sorry since childhood.
If you keep making trouble,
tell your husband to prepare for bankruptcy.
This is the medical expenses.
Call the police
or take the money.
Go back and discuss it with your husband.
I, Lu Qianqian,
will accompany you to the end.
Go.
You've regressed.
You've progressed too fast.
This sword school
is an exact replica.
You really like that sword school in France.
After returning from France,
I became obsessed with our encounter that day.
So,
I recreated this fencing hall
exactly as it was.
But you kept avoiding me when I approached.
Because, as you said,
I was afraid.
Not afraid anymore?
Still afraid.
But wild grass
will naturally entangle
with other weeds.
Isn't it?
Your words to coax people
are as exquisite as sword techniques.
No wonder Lu Qianqian is so devoted to you.
Compared with you,
I think I still have room for improvement.
I'll take a bath first.
It looks so real.
Did brother-in-law paint it?
He still can't forget that woman.
With your status and position,
is it worth it for that woman
who doesn't love you?
He's your brother-in-law.
I won't say it if you don't like to hear it.
What are you doing?
When I was a child and I was unhappy,
you would coax me with juice.
Today,
I'll have a couple of drinks with you.
What?
Are you afraid you can't drink me under the table?
Our son was bullied at school,
and fought with other children.
You don't go back to be with him,
but book this restaurant
to have a candlelight dinner with me.
Lu's children don't need to be indulged.
If there's really a problem,
Lu's people will solve it.
You're really a good father.
Do you know
why Xiao Mumu's name is Lu Mu
instead of Zhou Mu?
I...
I don't even have a child with my last name.
I don't deserve them.
I'm not worthy.
So, compared to a father,
I'm more like
an assigned administrator.
The life of a wealthy family that makes countless people jealous.
Under this golden and jade garment,
there is indeed only a bone
without temperature and flesh.
It's really ironic and realistic.
Don't you really consider Zhuang Wan's proposal?
She can give you much more than this.
Change a yard,
and be another gatekeeper.
Do you think there's any difference?
I've been waiting for an opportunity,
to completely change Lu Mu
into Zhou Mu
by my own strength.
Then let's create this opportunity together.
Do you know why I chose to take over this restaurant?
Because this is
the best platform overlooking the Golden Thread and Lu family.
From now on,
you are my ally
and my only accomplice.
Love
is just a well-planned scam by dopamine.
It first gives you a piece of candy,
then forces you to swallow ten pounds of broken glass.
It says it's eternal,
but in reality, it's shorter than the shelf life
of discounted fruits wrapped in plastic film in supermarkets.
Yesterday, you said I was your destiny.
Zhou Jian.
Tomorrow, it can turn into
we are not compatible in personality.
Zhou Jian, don't go!
Don't leave me!
The most passionate actor,
even the ring is a prop.
After filming, it has to be returned to the makeup team.
Do you know why fairy tales only go up to the wedding?
Because after that, it has to be turned into a suspense film.
Guess who cheats first,
who's scheming over property,
and whose "love forever"
gets withdrawn first.
Anyone who believes in love tied to interests
will end up lining up and drawing numbers
between the Civil Affairs Bureau and the mental hospital.
Jiang Li's live stream has you cornered.
Now only I can help you.
I'm coming to you.
Brother-in-law.
You're done.